■ gullandrea693@gmail.com | 🛠 handgull.netlify.app | 🖸 github.com/handgull | 🛅 linkedin.com/in/handgull



### **Presentation**

My name is Andrea, I am born in 1996 and I have successfully developed the good habit of continuous learning, thanks to the book "Atomic Habits". I enjoy creating and designing useful things with a simple UI.

I don't like using outdated tools or working in environments where the architecture is not valued (since the paycheck will come later).

Check my personal side project app: **ZYME** available on android and iOS! It's a calories counter, i hope you will like it!

# Skills (In order of proficiency) \_

I consider myself mainly a frontend developer, but I also have experience as a full-stack. I have already worked with microservices and microfrontends too! Lately i am playing with gen AI (LLMs, RAGs, NLP...)

Frontend Angular (Reactive programming lover), Flutter (Bloc and Provider for the DI), React (Redux / Jotai / Zustand as state managers).

**Backend** Node.js (Nest.js, Fastify as main choices), PostgreSQL (usually with PrismaORM or DrizzleORM), LangChain (novice level).

Infrastructure Git (usually with CI and PRs), Docker, RabbitMQ, Kubernetes, Linux, Terraform, Firebase / Supabase.

**Soft Skills** Agile method, Ability to provide precise estimates, Teamwork, Adaptability, Empathy, Pair programming.

### Education

ITIS (Giacomo Fauser) Novara, Italy Set. 2010 - Aug. 2015

High school diploma, computer science

Milano, Italy

Bachelor degree, computer science

• LEFT STUDIES at my 3rd year, with 4 exams left. I noticed that I couldn't study and work since I was already studying for work.

# Work Experience (5+ yrs)\_

**Freelancer** Comignago (NO), Italy

Mobile/Web Developer Feb 2022 - NOW

- Working with Angular since 2018.
- Working with Flutter since 2020.
- Working with Node.js since 2018.

**Ennova research** Lomazzo (CO), Italy May 2021 - Feb 2022

**Software Engineer** 

• We worked in big teams, divided in sub-teams according to the **AGILE** method

- Worked in big projects for clients like FAAC, Leroy Merlin, Eni etc...
- Technical Skills: Angular, React, Flutter.

**SOFTECH** Gallarate (VA), Italy Sep 2018 - Feb 2020

Junior developer

- SOFTECH offers systems, software and complete services in the field of monitoring and supervision of human interactions with the environment
- Developing external commissions as a full-stack novice.
- · Making implementation choices and constantly looking for news/technologies that could benefit the company
- Developing frontend of one of my company's biggest projects (airport industry)
- Technical Skills: Angular, Node. is, Leaflet and GIS Databases.

# Secondary interests \_

I love to study **nutrition** and **working out**! Proud owner of a **pet hedgehog** named Kenny. 🤏

# **Languages**\_

**English** Good reader, troubles forming complex sentences during a heavily technical conversation, but I make myself understood. Italiano Native proficiency.

Thankfully generative AI is a really promising helper in this field, i can self host a SLM (so there are no privacy issues) to provide real time translations and more!